RESUME

CHRIS ZBROJKIEWICZ

Frontend Developer

I am a passionate Frontend Developer with an interest in interface design and user experience.

I love bringing ideas to life by creating websites delivering the best user experience.

I have a keen eye for design, performance, and well-structured code.

I am dedicated to the best practice technologies and I focus on responsiveness and accessibility.

PROFILE

Country

United Kingdom

Phone

+44 078 35 57 57 59

Languages

English Polish

Email

chris.z@aol.com

Github

github.com/Chris-Z-85

LinkedIN

linkedin.com/in/ChrisZ85

PORTFOLIO

Website

chris-z.netlify.app/

EDUCATION

2020- 2020 Full Stack Web Development

Spiced Academy, Germany

2005 - 2010 MA: English, BA: Information Technology

University of Silesia, Poland

EMPLOYMENT

2019- 2020 Teacher of English

Self-employed, Germany & UK

2018 - 2019 Telematics User Support Specialist

Bosch, Germany

SKILLS

Core

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- Git & Github

Additional

- React
- Redux
- SASS & BEM
- RESTful API